movies4u.eu 2012-09-23

# Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect about you at [Movies4u](http://movies4u.eu/) (the "Website") and how we use this information. 

**Collection of your Movies4u Information** Your "Movies4u information" includes certain technical information gathered or received when you use Movies4u. Some of the technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; information about the version of service from an affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; other information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider. This information are collected by using the google analytics service. 

Movies4u does not require registration in order to view all site pages. This might change in the future. The only page where information like "email" are required is the contact page. 

### How Your Movies4u information is Used

Your Movies4u information is used: 

  * to operate and improve the websites, services and offerings available through Blend Series; 
  * to personalize the content provided to you; 
  * to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; 
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; 
  * to conduct research about your use of Blend Series; and 
  * to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

Your Movies4u information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a request, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your Movies4u information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your Movies4u information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of Movies4u users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

Cookies are text files that are placed in your computers browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a Movies4u user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browsers settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain Movies4u offerings. 

Movies4u and its advertisers may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on Movies4u. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event we utilize the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks. 

### Security

We have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your Movies4u information, but cannot guarantee that this information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers). 

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about Movies4u s Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by going to the following link: <http://movies4u.eu/contact.php>. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to Movies4u information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from Movies4u , as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.
